Guide to the Douglas Bennet Papers, 1940 - 2004
Douglas Bennet Papers,1940 - 2004
- Series I: Executive service, 1962-1995
  - State Department
    - Administrator for the Agency for International Development (AID), 1979 July-1981 January
      - Chron files
        - 1979 June-November (Box 12, Folder 3-8)
        - 1979 December-1980 September (Box 13, Folder 1-10)
        - 1980 October-1981 March (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
      - AID trips and photographs
        - Travel, 1978 October-1980 October (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - Middle East trip, 1979 September 15-30 (Box 14, Folder 7)
        - Israel, photographs, 1979 September 16-19 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        - Jordan, photographs, 1979 September 19-21 (Box 14, Folder 9)
        - Egypt, photographs, 1979 September 23-25 (Box 14, Folder 10)
        - Yemen, personal photos, 1979 September 25-29 (Box 14, Folder 11)
        - Yemen, Bennet/Wheeler trip, 1979 September 25-29 (Box 14, Folder 12)
        - Latin America, 1979 November 13-16 (Box 15, Folder 1)
        - Costa Rica, photographs, 1979 November (Box 15, Folder 2-4)
        - Detroit conference, U.S. foreign policy in Africa, 1979 December 13 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        - Asia, 1980 January 15-February 3 (Box 15, Folder 6)
        - Sri Lanka, photographs, 1980 January 21-February 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
        - Dallas, American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1980 February 28-29 (Box 15, Folder 8)
        - Williamsburg conference, The Presidency, Congress and U.S. Global Leadership, 1980 April 18-20 (Box 15, Folder 9)
        - New York, The Third World: U.S. Opportunites for Survival, 1980 May 23 (Box 15, Folder 10)
        - California, Foreign Aid in a Turbulent World, 1980 June 2-3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
        - Hartford, CT, U.S. Opportunities in a Fast-changing Third World, 1980 June 16 (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - London, 1980 July 4-15 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - Nicaragua/Panama, 1980 August 3-7 (Box 16, Folder 4)
        - Panama, Bennet/Vaughn photographs, 1980 August 4-7 (Box 16, Folder 5)
        - Rome, FAO African food conference, 1980 September 17-20 (Box 16, Folder 6)
        - Africa, 1980 September 25-October 11 (Box 16, Folder 7)
        - Mauritania, Nouakchott photographs, 1980 September (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
        - Upper Volta photographs, 1980 September-October (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
        - New Orleans, 1980 October 24 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        - New York, 1980 October 29 (Box 17, Folder 2)
        - Ottawa, 1980 November 13-16 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - General photographs (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
        - Publicity photographs (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Subject files
        - Audiotape: E79-1 Morning Plenary Session, Economic Club of Detroit, 1979 December? (Box 92 [oversize])
        - Audiotapes: A.I.D., sides 1 and 2, 1980 December 15 (Box 92 [oversize])
        - Audiotape: [unlabeled], undated (Box 92 [oversize])
        - Clippings, 1972-1980 (Box 88 [oversize], Folder 5)
        - Council on foreign relations, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Departure, 1981 January (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Departure, 1981 January (Box 93 [oversize], Folder 5)
        - Departure luncheon, 1981 January 13 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - Education, 1980 March (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - Hold for Doug, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        - IDCA - redundancy file, 1980 July-August (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - IDCA - relationship, 1979 December-1981 January (Box 18, Folder 1-5)
        - IDCA - reorganization, 1979 April-July (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
        - IDCA - history, 1980 July-August (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - ISTC, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Memoranda of conversation, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - Order of the Plimsoll Mark, 1980 October 24 (Box 93 [oversize], Folder 4)
        - Papers for administrator nomination, bulk 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
        - Prep, 1979 June-August (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Private file - NODIS, bulk 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
        - Project development procedures, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        - 5" reel tape, Doug Bennet before National War College: Economic Assistance as an Instrument of U.S. Foreign Policy, 1980 November 19 (Box 89 [oversize])
        - Regional administrators' visions, 1979 May-July (Box 19, Folder 6)
        - Videotape: Administrator's Address to AID Employees, 1979 August (Box 89 [oversize])
        - Videotape: AID 1980 Awards Ceremony, 42:00 (Box 90 [oversize])
        - Videotape: AID,Seeking the Delicate Balance, S.J. Staniski, 36:00, undated (Box 90 [oversize])
      - AID evaluations
        - Project impact evalutation reports, 1980 December-1981 June (Box 19, Folder 7-11)
        - Project impact evaluation reports, 1981 September-1982 October (Box 20, Folder 1-8)
        - Project impact evaluation reports, 1982 December-1984 February (Box 21, Folder 1-9)
        - Project impact evaluation reports, 1984 March, June (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
        - Program evaluation discussion papers, 1982 April-1984 September (Box 22, Folder 3-8)
        - Program evaluation reports, 1982 March (Box 22, Folder 9)
        - Program evaluation reports, 1982 August-1984 January (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
        - Evaluation special studies, 1981 July-1983 March (Box 23, Folder 6-8)
        - Evaluation special studies, 1983 March-1984 April (Box 24, Folder 1-5)
        - Evaluation working paper, 1983 November (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Program design and evaluation methods, 1984 January (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Lessons learned - evaluation report abstracts, 1981 September-1983 October (Box 24, Folder 8-10)
    - Assistant Secretary of State for International Organization Affairs, 1993 May-1995 May
      - Correspondence
        - Personal, 1993 March-1994 December (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
      - Subject files
        - Agenda for peace, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - The American assembly, Arden House, 1993 June 3-6 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - Audiotape: Secretary Christopher at luncheon, Bosnian-Croatian signing, 1994 March 18 (Box 92 [oversize])
        - Audiotape: Dumbarton Oaks speech (at State Department), 1994 May 5 (Box 92 [oversize])
        - Audiotape: Open foroum, Doug Bennet, 1994 November 21 (Box 92 [oversize])
        - Audiotapes: ASIL, tapes 3 and 4, Reforming the United Nations, Parts 1 and 2, 1994 (Box 92 [oversize])
        - Congressional testimony, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - Confirmation hearning, 1993 January-May (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - Grant, James P., 1995 January-February (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - I.O. Appointment, 1992 December-1993 September (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - News clips, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - Notes, 1993 March-May (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Personal, 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
        - Policy & Strategy, 1992 October-1995 April (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - Press, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - Rwanda, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Rosenau, James - papers, 1993, November 16 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
        - Sovereignty question, 1993 March 5 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - U.N., 1991 December-1992 July (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - U.N. speech material, 1974, 1990-1993 (Box 27, Folder 5-8)
        - U.N. speech material, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
        - U.N. speech material - clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
        - Videotape: NHK Japan Broadcasting Corp. UN PKO: A Somalian Perspective, 1993 November 11 (Box 91 [oversize])
        - Videotape: Assistant Secretary of State, Douglas Bennet on Rwandan Television, 1994 February 5 (Box 91 [oversize])
        - Videotapes #1 and #2, NHK Interview of Douglas Bennet by Junko Tanaka, 1994 March 24 (Box 91 [oversize])
        - Videotape: On the Line #60,The United Nations at Fifty, 20:00, 1995 February 9 (Box 91 [oversize])
        - Videotape: [card of public speaking expert attached], Assistant Secretary Bennet, undated (Box 91 [oversize])
        - Vouchers - taxi, telephone, etc., 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Speeches/press interviews
        - 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 5-7)
      - Phone logs
        - 1993 May-1995 May (Box 29, Folder 1-5)
  - Assistant to Vice-President Hubert H. Humphrey, 1967 July-1969 January
    - Correspondence, 1968 May-1969 January (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Looking back in 1982, 1982 July-August (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Resumes of consultants, possible employees, 1968 May-June (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - HHH selected speeches, 1967 July-1968 September (Box 30, Folder 4-7)
    - 1968 campaign
      - Convention (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Invitations (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Memos, etc., 1968 April-November (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
      - Publicity (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Realia: campaign buttons (Box 89 [oversize])
      - Realia: campaign materials (Box 93 [oversize], Folder 1)
      - Research materials
        - Agnew (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - HHH Vs. Nixon - & Wallace (Box 31, Folder 2-5)
        - Newspaper articles (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Nixon - debates (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - Nixon - personal financial worth (Box 31, Folder 8)
        - Nixon - rep. - crime (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - Nixon - speeches and quotes (Box 31, Folder 10)
        - P.R. 9/29 Nixon: crime piece - double talk (Box 31, Folder 11)
        - Securities Exchange letter - Nixon (Box 31, Folder 12)
        - Wallace (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Speeches
        - HHH (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
        - HHH, I-VIII (Box 32, Folder 4-6)
        - Unused speech drafts (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Task forces, 1968 July-August (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Series II: Legislative Service,1969-1977
  - Administrative Assistant to Senator Thomas F. Eagleton (MO), 1969 January-1973 March
    - Correspondence
      - Personal, 1969 January-1970 August (Box 32, Folder 9-12)
      - Personal, 1970 September-1972 August (Box 33, Folder 1-7)
    - Memos
      - Memos from Doug, 1969 January-December (Box 33, Folder 8-10)
      - Memos, 1970 January-December (Box 33, Folder 11-13)
      - Memos, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 1-7)
      - Memos, addendum, 1972 July-November (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Subject files
      - Bowles, Chester, 1967 August-1968 December (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - 7" reel tape: Ambassador Bowles' Remarks at Mission Staff Meeting, 1969 April 17 (Box 89 [oversize])
      - Clippings, 1968-1973 (Box 87 [oversize], Folder 1-6)
      - Office expenses, 1968-1973 (Box 34, Folder 10-13)
      - Research materials, 1960-1972 (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
      - Speeches, notes and drafts, 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Speeches, 1972, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Unused speech drafts, 1970 February, May (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - 1972 Campaign
        - Campaign, general, 1972 July (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - CT state Democratic lists, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 9)
        - Democratic convention (Box 35, Folder 10)
        - Democratic platform (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
        - Democratic platform (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
        - Fact book: the Nixon record, 1972 July (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - Fact book, update, 1972 July 18 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Muskie, 1971 April-1972 April (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Muskie campaign, 1972 March-June (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
        - Negative on other candidates, 1972 April (Box 36, Folder 8)
        - Nixon record on poverty and welfare, 1972 July 19 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - Organization file - 1972 VP, 1972 July (Box 36, Folder 10)
        - Realia: campaign buttons (Box 89 [oversize])
        - Reference materials (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - Richard Nixon and the special interests, 1972 July 17 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - 18 days, 1972 July-August (Box 37, Folder 3-5)
        - 18 days, oral history, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - 18 days, memo, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - Parting thoughts: an interview with Thomas Eagleton, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Assistant to Senator Abraham Ribicoff (CT), 1973 April-1974 April
    - The Center Magazine, 1973 May-August (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Memos, 1973 January-1974 March (Box 37, Folder 10-13)
  - Bennet 1974 Campaign for House of Representatives, 1974 April-August
    - Correspondence
      - Correspondence, A-Z (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Chronological, 1972 November-1973 February (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Contributor's letters, 1974 February-July (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - CT Democratic prospects, 1972 August-1973 February (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Inter-office, 1974 February-June (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Outgoing, A-Z (Box 38, Folder 3-6)
      - Thank-you letters, A-Z, 1974 April-July (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Post-campaigin (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Subject files
      - Advertising (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Announcement statement, 1974 April 30 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Bailey (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Budget (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Chron files, 1974 July 5-9 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Clippings (Box 88 [oversize], Folder 1-4)
      - Contacts (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Delegate cards (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Delegate cards (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
      - Delegate mailings (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Democratic town chairmen, mayors and delegates (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - DJB senior (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Dodd (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Dues: seminars, subscriptions (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Filing forms (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - June 10 reports (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - 15th day reports (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - 5th day filings (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Financial (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Fundraising (Box 39, Folder 13-15)
      - Fundraiser, Washington, 1974 June 5 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Invitations extended and accepted (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Meals (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Misc. (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Nominating speech, drafts, copy (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Office supplies/rent (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Old, reimbursable forms (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Peck (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Past schedules and notes (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Planning (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Political activists (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Postage (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Presentation (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Press (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Press releases (Box 40, Folder 15-16)
      - Printing (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Promotion (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Promotion (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
      - Registration papers, info, etc. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Resumes, support services, consultants (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Savage (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Schonberger (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - 2nd district Democratic town chairmen, mayors and delegates, 1974 April 15 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Speeches (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Speech material (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Steele-Ribicoff poll, 1973 July-December (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Telephone (Box 41, Folder 11-12)
      - Town chairman/chief of Demo.'s letter with enclosures, 1974 April 8 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Travel (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Vinyl, 45 rpm: Watergate Bugs by Les Waldroop, 1974 (Box 89 [oversize])
      - Willing workers (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Staff Director of Senate Budget Committee, 1974 September-1977 March
    - Chron files
      - 1974 September-1976 March (Box 42, Folder 1-12)
      - 1976 April-1976 December (Box 43, Folder 1-9)
    - Subject files
      - General correspondence, 1974 September-December (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - European trip, 1976 January (Box 43, Folder 11-12)
      - Invitations and speaking engagements, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Invitations, 1976 February (Box 43, Folder 14-15)
      - Invitations, 1976 April-December (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Search for CBO director, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Speaking engagements, 1974 October-1975 December (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
      - Speaking engagements, Maine Teacher's Association, 1976 October 1 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Speeches, not for ESM, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Staff directory, 1976 October 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Travel expenses, 1975 February (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Senate Budget Committee History
      - Budget process book, parts I and II
        - Part I (Box 44, Folder 10-13)
        - Part I (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
        - Part I, back-up (Box 45, Folder 3)
        - Chronology, 1975 January 1-March 18 (Box 45, Folder 4-8)
        - Part II (Box 46, Folder 1-5)
        - Chronology, 1975 March 19-May 15 (Box 46, Folder 6-9)
      - Separate notebooks, documents
        - C-2 (Box 47, Folder 1)
        - C-3 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - C-4 (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - 4-A (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - 4-Supplemental (Box 47, Folder 5-6)
        - C-5 (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - C-6 (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - C-7: Trade-offs (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - C-8: March 18 committee reports (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
        - C-9: Cohn report (Box 48, Folder 6)
        - C-10: Transcripts of trade-off meetings, 1975 March 20-21 (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - C-11: Transcripts of trade-off meetings, 1975 April 8 (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - C-11: Transcripts of trade-off meetings, 1975 April 9 (Box 49, Folder 3-4)
        - C-11: Transcripts of trade-off meetings, 1975 April 10 (Box 49, Folder 5-6)
        - C-11: Transcripts of trade-off meetings, 1975 April 11 (Box 49, Folder 7-8)
        - C-11: Mark-ups on trade-offs, 1975 April 8-11 (Box 49, Folder 9-10)
        - C-12: Floor management background, 1975 April 29-May 1 (Box 49, Folder 11)
        - C-13: Conference on first concurrent resolution (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
        - Outlay section (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
        - Allowances (Box 50, Folder 5-7)
        - Congressional Record - debate, 1975 April 29-May 1 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - First concurrent resolution, 1976
        - Memos and correspondence, 1974 December-1975 May (Box 50, Folder 9)
        - President's budget, 1975 January-February (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous notes, 1975 March-April (Box 50, Folder 11)
        - Mark-up, 1975 March-September (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - [unlabeled], 1975 April (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - Conference report, 1975 May 6-12 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Scorekeeping, 1975 June-September (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - Reconciliation, 1975 September (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - Revenues, 1975 September (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Second concurrent resolution, 1976
        - Memos and correspondence, 1975 June-December (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - Schedule for 1976, 1975 December (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - Hearing transcripts, 1975 October 21-30 (Box 51, Folder 9-11)
        - Preparation for markup - key (Box 51, Folder 12)
        - Preparation for markup, tab A (Box 51, Folder 13)
        - Preparation for markup, tabs B-H (Box 52, Folder 1-9)
        - Markup session transcript, 1975 November 4 (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - Markup session transcripts, 1975 November 5-12 (Box 53, Folder 1-4)
        - Conference transcripts, 1975 December 3-8 (Box 53, Folder 5-7)
        - Outlay shortfall, 1976 October-1977 January (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - First concurrent resolution, 1977
        - Preparation, 1975 December (Box 53, Folder 9)
        - Review of President's budget, 1976 January-February (Box 53, Folder 10)
        - Candidate issues, 1975 November-1976 February (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
        - Hearings, 1976 January-March (Box 54, Folder 3)
        - March 15 committee reports, 1976 January-March (Box 54, Folder 4)
        - Markup materials, 1976 March (Box 54, Folder 5-7)
        - Floor action, 1976 April (Box 54, Folder 8)
        - Report, 1976 April (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
        - Conference, 1976 April-May (Box 55, Folder 3)
        - Tax expenditures, 1976 April-May (Box 55, Folder 4)
        - Letter to all staff directors, 1976 May (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - Budget status reports, 1976 July (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Second concurrent resoluation, 1977
        - Preparation for: memos and correspondence, 1976 July-September (Box 55, Folder 7)
        - Markup materials, 1976 August (Box 55, Folder 8-9)
        - Markup materials, 1976 August (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
        - Hearing, Thursday August 26, 1976 August (Box 56, Folder 4)
        - Floor debate, 1976 August-September (Box 56, Folder 5-6)
        - Conference, 1976 September (Box 56, Folder 7)
        - Conference report, floor debate and final passage, 1976 September (Box 56, Folder 8)
        - Crosswalk reports, 1976 September-October (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Clips and articles, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
      - Editorials and feature articles, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
      - Review of President Ford's budget for FY'78, 1977 January (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Series III: Roosevelt Center for American Policy Studies,1981-1983
  - Chron files
    - 1981 April-1982 April (Box 57, Folder 7-13)
    - 1982 May-December (Box 58, Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 January-June (Box 59, Folder 1-11)
    - 1983 June-October (Box 60, Folder 1-4)
  - Subject files
    - Activities reports, 1983 March-June (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - American Assembly, 1982 April 15-18 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - American Enterprise Institute conference, 1982 January 7 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Aspen Institute, 1982 February-November (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Bennet, Douglas, publications, 1978-1981 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - DB personal papers on "Institute" (from blue folder), 1981 July-August (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - California trip, 1982 February 14-17 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - California trip, 1983 April 4-8 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Celeste, Richard F. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Center for European Policy Studies, 1982 June-December (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Connecticut trip, 1982 February 11-12 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Contacts, 1981-1983 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Dennis, institute expenses, 1981 June-December (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Eagleton, Thomas F., article, 1982 January (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - EST Foundation meeting, 1983 March 20-22 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Expenses, 1981 November-1983 April (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - First year objectives, 1982 January-April (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - First year report, 1983 May 1 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Humphrey, H.H. - Carl Solberg correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Invitations completed, 1981 January-October (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Issue file, foreign policy, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Issue file, U.S. economy, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Kettering Foundation, 1983 August-September (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda of conversation, 1981 November-1983 May (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - New World Foundation, 1981 June (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - New World Foundation, project memoranda, 1981 February-July (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Press, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Publication: Brown, Melissa, "Tax Choices,", 1983 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Richardson, Elliot L., 1982 September (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Rockefeller correspondence, 1981 August-October (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, DB consultant material, 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Tokyo trip, October 21-31, 1982, 1982 February-November (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Tokyo trip, May 13-14, 1983, 1983 April-May (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Urban Institute, 1983 September-October (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Vance speech, 1981 October 5 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - White, Arthur (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Wingspread, March 18-21, 1982, 1982 January-August (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Board meetings
    - May 5, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - June 22-23, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - October 12-13, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 10-11)
    - Minutes of May, June and October meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Februaryruary 2-3, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
  - Resignation and departure
    - Dennis-Bennet correspondence, 1983 January-Jun (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Prep for RD meeting, 1983 June 15 (Box 63, Folder 4-5)